One Starry Christmas is a tv movie, romance film directed by John Bradshaw.
An aspiring astronomy professor finds unexpected Christmas romance when
she meets a charming cowboy during her holiday travel.
As she decides between this new cowboy and her practical boyfriend, she must decide whether it's
better to play it safe in love, or let an adventurous cowboy steal her heart.
Holly Jensen, played by Sarah Carter.
Luke Shelton, played by Damon Runyan.
Adam, played by Paul Popowich.
Betsy Jensen, played by Kathleen Laskey.
Ken Jensen, played by Neil Crone.
Bull, played by George Canyon.
Ron Howard is an American director, producer, screenwriter, and actor.
He started his career portraying Opie, the son of Andy Taylor (played by Andy Griffith) in the sitcom The Andy Griffith Show
from 1960 through 1968 and Richie Cunningham in the sitcom Happy Days, a role he would play from 1974 to 1980.
During this time, he also acted in films such as The Music Man
(1962), American Graffiti (1973), and The Shootist (1976).
Howard retired from acting in 1980.
He then shifted into directing comedies such as Night Shift (1982), Splash (1984), and Cocoon (1985) as well as
the fantasy Willow (1988), the thriller Backdraft (1991), and the newspaper film The Paper (1994).
He then transitioned into directing critically acclaimed dramas such as Apollo 13 (1995), A Beautiful Mind
(2001), Cinderella Man (2005), Frost/Nixon (2008), Rush (2013), and In the Heart of the Sea (2015).
Howard also directed the children's film How the Grinch Stole Christmas (2000) as well as the Robert Langdon film
series, The Da Vinci Code (2006), Angels & Demons (2009), Inferno (2016), and Solo: A Star Wars Story (2018).
He has also directed the documentary films The Beatles:
Eight Days a Week (2016) and Pavarotti (2019).
The tone is emotional.